<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<topic xmlns="">
  <title>Configuring your Software Firewall</title>
  <p>
    A firewall monitors and controls the traffic coming into and out of your account. The traffic of the Internet consists of information which takes the form of data packets. A firewall evaluates each data packet and determines whether or not to pass the packet to your account. For example, a firewall can prevent your account from receiving an overwhelming quantity of unwanted traffic. Some of the unwanted traffic may be simply bothersome. Other traffic may actually be sent from malicious Internet users who intend to make your account inoperable. Either way, building a firewall is an important configuration task for you to consider.
  </p>
  <p><em type="bold">Note: </em>The firewall can only be configured by the System Administrator.
  </p>
  <ol title="To Configure Your Firewall: ">
      <li><p>In the System Administration menu group, click <em type="bold">Software Firewall</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
	  <p>The Software Firewall page appears.</p>
	  </li>
      <li>Select the security level the firewall should use for your account.
	  <p><em type="bold">Note: </em>When you specify <em type="italic">low</em> firewall security, your account blocks port-scan attempts, spoofing attempts, and remote loopback attacks.</p>
	  <p> When you specify <em type="italic">medium</em> firewall security, all of the low security firewall settings apply. In addition, specific security criteria are added to your account’s firewall so that only essential and convenient ports and protocols are allowed.</p>
	  <p>When you specify <em type="italic">high</em> firewall security, all of the low security firewall settings apply. In addition, specific security criteria are added to your account’s firewall so that only essential secure ports and protocols are allowed.</p>
	  </li>
	  <li>Select the server type the firewall should use for your account.
	  <p><em type="bold">Note: </em>As well as specifying a firewall security level for your account, you can specify the server types for which the firewall security settings apply. You can specify that the firewall security settings apply to both Mail and Web ports, or only to Web ports.</p>
	  </li>
	  <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. A message appears confirming the configuration has been applied.</li>
    </ol>
	<p>In addition to the above information about software firewall levels, the following information describes software firewall levels in more detail:</p>
  <ul title="When you specify low security (level 1), only the following ICMP packet types are processed:">
  		<li><em type="bold">0 (outgoing ping)</em> You can use the ping computer network tool to verify whether a particular host is reachable. The tool sends an ICMP Echo Request and listens for a reply. When you specify a low security setting for your account, it may send outgoing ping packets only. Your account will not reply to another host’s ping.</li>
		<li><em type="bold">3 (destination unreachable)</em> Your account will process ICMP packets which are generated by another host These packets are received when a designated transport protocol is unable to process data in the transport layer and the remote system or host has no means of replying with that information.</li>
		<li><em type="bold">4 (source quench)</em> A remote host may discard data if it does not have the buffer space needed to queue the data for output to the next network on the route to the destination host. When you specify low security, your account will process ICMP packets which indicate this has occurred.</li>
		<li><em type="bold">11(timeout)</em> A remote host may not reply or acknowledge your account’s sent data in sufficient time. When you specify low security, your account will process ICMP packets which indicate this has occurred.</li>
		<li><em type="bold">12 (parameter problems)</em> A remote host cannot process a packet due to a problem in the packet header (or, possibly, an incorrect argument in an option). The remote host has discarded the packet and has sent this ICMP packet to your account. When you specify low security, your account processed this type of ICMP packet.</li>
		</ul>
	<ul title="When you specify medium security (level 2), only the following services, ports, and protocols are allowed:">
		<ul title="TCP Protocol">
			<li>FTP-S (ports 989, 990)</li>
			<li>SSH (port 22)</li>
			<li>Telnet-S (port 992)</li>
			<li>SMTP (port 25)</li>
			<li>SMTP-S (port 465)</li>
			<li>HTTP (port 80)</li>
			<li>HTTP-S (port 443)</li>
			<li>Web cache (port 8080)</li>
			<li>POP3 (port 110)</li>
			<li>POP3-S (port 995)</li>
			<li>IMAP (port 143)</li>
			<li>IMAP-S (port 993)</li>
			<li>DNS client (port 53)</li>
			<li>NTP client (port 123)</li>
			<li>Outbound Auth, or <em type="italics">identd</em> (port 113)</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="UDP Protocol">
			<li>DNS client (port 53)</li>
			<li>NTP client (port 123)</li>
		</ul>
	</ul>
	<ul title="When you specify high security (level 3), only the following services, ports, and protocols are allowed:">
		<ul title="TCP Protocol">
			<li>SSH (port 22)</li>
			<li>SMTP (port 25)</li>
			<li>SMTP-S (port 465)</li>
			<li>HTTP (port 80)</li>
			<li>HTTP-S (port 443)</li>
			<li>Web cache (port 8080)</li>
			<li>POP3-S (port 995)</li>
			<li>IMAP-S (port 993)</li>
			<li>DNS client (port 53)</li>
			<li>NTP client (port 123)</li>
			<li>Outbound Auth, or <em type="italics">identd</em> (port 113)</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="UDP Protocol">
			<li>DNS client (port 53)</li>
			<li>NTP client (port 123)</li>
		</ul>
	</ul>
</topic>
