<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<topic xmlns="">
  <title>iTunes Podcast Channel Information Fields</title>
  <p>You can use this feature to complete the iTunes Information fields for a podcast channel.</p>
  <ol title="To complete the iTunes Channel Information Fields:">
  <p><em type="bold">Important:</em> The iTunes Information section is an optional part of the podcasting process. If you want to join the iTunes podcast directory, complete the iTunes information fields to provide more information to iTunes podcasts directory users.</p>
    <li><p>Click <em type="bold">Show iTunes Information</em>. The window expands displaying the iTunes information fields.</p>
	</li>
	<li><p>Enter the information about your channel in the appropriate fields.</p>
	<p><em type="bold">Note:</em> Clicking <em type="bold">Hide iTunes Information</em> collapses the window to hide the iTunes information fields.</p>
	<ul title="The following explains each field:">
		<li><em type="bold">Subtitle:</em> A subtitle for the channel (for example: A show about everything).
		</li>
		<li><em type="bold">Content Author:</em> The name of the channel author (for example: John Smith).
		</li>
		<li><em type="bold">Summary:</em> A brief description of the channel (for example: A look at my music.).
		</li>
		<li><em type="bold">Category:</em> The type of podcast and the topics related to the Category. Some examples are Category: <em type="italic">Arts and Entertainment</em> Topics: <em type="italic">Books, Games, Poetry</em>, Category: <em type="italic">Business</em> Topics: <em type="italic">Careers, Inverting</em>, Category: <em type="italic">Technology</em> Topics: <em type="italic">Computers, Operating Systems</em>. Select a Topic you want. For multiple selections, hold down the 'Ctrl' key.
		</li>
		<li><em type="bold">Owner:</em> The owner of the channel (for example: John Smith).
		</li>
		<li><em type="bold">E-Mail:</em> The channel owner's e-mail address (for example: john@example.com).
		</li>
		<li><p><em type="bold">Podcast URL Image:</em> The URL where the podcast images are stored (for example: http://www.example.com/image).</p>
			<p><em type="bold">Important:</em> The Podcast image size cannot exceed a maximum of 300 x 300 pixels.</p>
		</li>
		<li><em type="bold">Explicit Content:</em> A warning that this podcast episode might contain material inappropriate or offensive to some people. The options are: <em type="bold">Yes</em> if the content is explicit and <em type="bold">No</em> if the content is not explicit.
		</li>
		<li><em type="bold">Block Content:</em> Selecting the <em type="bold">Yes</em> checkbox prevents the podcast episode from being listed in the iTunes podcasts directory. Deselecting the Yes checkbox enables the podcast feed to be displayed in the iTunes podcasts directory.
		</li>
	</ul>
	<p><em type="bold">Note:</em> If you want to register your podcast channels to the Podcast Directory in the iTunes Music Store, go to <a topic="h_pc_registering_podcast_to_a_podcasts_directory">Registering Your Podcast Channel and Episodes to a Podcast Directory</a>.</p>
	</li>
  </ol>
</topic>
