<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<topic xmlns="">
  <title>Control Panel Getting Started Guide</title>
  <p>Welcome to your Control Panel Help! These files are designed to ensure that you are able to use all of the features of 

your new account. Help can be accessed from any window in your control panel, but this file is designed to give you an 

overview of how your new account works, and provide you with links to more detailed information.</p>
  <p>
    <em type="bold">Note:</em> You can print this file and keep a hard copy to reference later if you have issues with your 

control panel.
  </p>
  <section-list title="Sections of the Getting Started Guide:" />
  <section id="Logging_In_to_Your_Contro_Panel" title="Logging In to Your Control Panel">
<ol title="Logging In to Your Control Panel">
</ol>          
<p>
    <em type="bold">Important:</em> In order to keep your passwords secure, you should always log in to your Control Panel 

via https, not http.
  </p>

     <p>Obviously, if you are reading this you know how to log into your control panel. But you can provide instructions for 

logging in to your sub-users, if you want.</p>
    <ol title="To log in to your Control Panel:">
      <li>Start your Web browser.</li>
      <li>Type <em type="bold">https://</em>
        <em type="italic">your_domain</em>
        <em type="bold">/ControlPanel/</em> in the address bar; then press <em type="bold">Enter</em>. (Replace your_domain 

with your domain name). The Login window appears.
      </li>
      <li>Type your user ID and password in the appropriate fields.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Login</em>. The Control Panel appears. If your user ID/password combination does not work, 

try logging in again. If the login still does not work, contact Support.
      </li>
    </ol>
  </section>
  <section id="Changing_Your_Password" title="Changing Your Password">
 <ol title="Changing Your Password">
</ol>   
<p>
      <em type="bold">Important:</em> You should change your password right after logging into your account for the first 

time.
    </p>
    <p>
      <em type="bold">Caution:</em> Hackers devote a significant amount of money and time to find and decipher passwords. 

Creating your password as a non-dictionary, alphanumeric combination using upper and lower case letters will go a long way 

toward protecting your server from such attacks.
    </p>
    <ol title="To change your password: ">
 <li><p>In the My Profile menu group, click <em type="bold">Change My Password</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Change My Password window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>Type your new password in the New Password field.</li>
      <li>Type your new password again in the Confirm Password field.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. A message appears informing you that your changes have been saved.
      </li>
    </ol>
  </section>
  <section id="Logging_Out_of_Your_Control_Panel" title="Logging Out of Your Control Panel">
<ol title="Logging Out of Your Control Panel">
</ol>  
    <p>To log out, click <em type="bold">Logout</em> in the upper-right corner.
    </p>
  </section>
  <section id="Automatic_Logout" title="Automatic Logout">
<ol title="Automatic Logout">
</ol>  
    <p>You can set the length of time that you want your system to remain logged on after it becomes idle.</p>
    <ol title="To set your automatic-logout time duration:">
 <li><p>In the My Preferences menu group, click <em type="bold">Auto-Logout</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Auto-Logout Preferences window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>Next to Logout, select how long you want your system to remain logged on after it becomes idle (1, 2, 8, or 24 

hours).</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. A message appears informing you that your changes have been saved.<p>
          <em type="bold">Note:</em> When the system automatically ends your session and you attempt to do anything in your 

Control Panel, the Login screen appears. Type your user ID and password; then click <em type="bold">Login</em> to start a new 

session.
        </p>
      </li>
    </ol>
  </section>
  <section id="Setting_Your_Server_Time_Zone" title="Setting Your Server Time Zone" user_access_level='DA'>
<ol title="Setting Your Server Time Zone">
</ol>  
    <p>Many time-sensitive tasks and records are tied to your server time zone.</p>
    <p>
      <em type="bold">Note:</em> Greenwich Mean Time (GMT) is the default setting for these servers.  If you change the 

server time from GMT, you should ensure that you have the appropriate time zone set for your cron jobs or other processes.
    </p>
    <ol title="To Set Your Server Time Zone:">
 <li><p>In the System Administration menu group, click <em type="bold">Set Server Time Zone</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Set Server Time Zone window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>Click the Time Zone drop down menu to view a list of time zones.</li>
      <li>Select the time zone you want.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>.
      </li>
      <li>Your VPS sets the time zone when you reboot the server. To reboot your VPS, click <em type="bold">Manage 

Services</em>.
      </li>
      <li>The Manage Services window appears. Click <em type="bold">reboot</em> in the server line.
      </li>
      <li>The Server reboots, and uses your new time zone going forward.</li>
    </ol>
  </section>
  <section id="Viewing_Account_Information" title="Viewing Account Information" user_access_level='DA'>
<ol title="Viewing Account Information">
</ol>  
    <p>Your Account Information window provides you with the following information:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Your Server Name, displaying the name you have assigned to this server.</li>
      <li>The server I.P. Address, displaying the location of the server on the Internet.</li>
      <li>Disk Usage figure, displaying how much disk space you have used and have left.</li>
      <li>Number of Open Files, displaying what files are opened in your File Manager.</li>
      <li>Number of Processes, displaying the jobs running on your VPS.</li>
      <li>Number of Virtual Hosts, describing how many virtual hosts you have set up.</li>
      <li>Number of Users, describing how many users you have set up.</li>
    </ul>
    <ol title="To view your account information:">
 <li><p>In the System Administration menu group, click <em type="bold">View Account Information</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The View Account Information window appears, displaying your account information.</p>
		</li>
    </ol>
  </section>
  <section id="Viewing_the_Home_Directory" title="Viewing Your Home Directory" user_attrib_level='fileman'>
<ol title="Viewing Your Home Directory">
</ol> 
    <p>The File Manager defaults to display the account owner's directory.</p>
    <p>To view your home directory:</p>
 <li><p>In the File Management menu group, click <em type="bold">File List</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The File List window appears.</p>
		</li>
  </section>
  <section id="Editing_the_Mail_Catchall" title="Editing the Mail Catchall" user_access_level='DA'>
<ol title="Editing the Mail Catchall">
</ol> 
    <p>The catchall email address receives all email that is not specifically routed to an existing mailbox (including mail 

with the correct domain, but with an incorrectly spelled email name).</p>
    <p>
      <em type="bold">Important:</em> Consider carefully how you use this feature; the catchall address might receive a lot 

of spam.
    </p>
    <ol title="To edit an account's mail catchall: ">
 <li><p>In the Domain Management menu group, click <em type="bold">Domain List</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Domain List window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>In the Actions column, click <em type="bold">properties</em> for the domain you want to edit. The Properties window 

for the selected domain appears.
      </li>
      <li>Next to Domain Setup, click <em type="bold">Edit</em>. The Edit Domain Setup window appears.
      </li>
      <li>Next to Mail Catchall, select the option you want. If you want catchall mail delivered to a specific address, 

select Deliver mail to and type that address in the Deliver mail to field.<p>
          <em type="bold">Note:</em> If you type multiple addresses, separate each one with a comma.
        </p>
      </li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. A message appears informing you that your domain has been changed.
      </li>
    </ol>
  </section>
  <section id="Adding_Email_Addresses" title="Adding Email Addresses" user_access_level='DA'>
<ol title="Adding Email Addresses">
</ol> 
    <p>You will want to create email addresses for your account. You can add as many email addresses as you want.</p>
    <ol title="To add an email address: ">
 <li><p>In the Mail System menu group, click <em type="bold">Email Addresses</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Email Addresses window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Add Email Address...</em>. The Add Email Address window appears.</li>
      <li>Type the email address you want in the Email Address: field.</li>
      <li>Select the domain you want from the @ drop-down list.</li>
      <li>Select a Mail Delivery option. The Mail Delivery option affects all incoming messages sent to this email address. 

Incoming mail may be rejected, deleted, or delivered to one or more recipients. Mail delivery recipients can include either a 

local user, or (one or more) external email addresses. For local recipients, select the local user you want from the Local 

mailbox - deliver to user drop-down list.  For one or more external email addresses type each full external email address in 

the List - Deliver mail to the following... field.<p>
          <em type="bold">Note:</em> If you type multiple addresses, separate each one with a comma or place different email 

addresses on separate lines.
        </p>
      </li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. The Email Addresses window reappears with a message stating that your new address 

has been added.
      </li>
    </ol>
  </section>

</topic>
