<faq>
<category id='system_administration' title='System Administration'>
  <question id='2' title="How can I access the control panel interface from the web?"><answer>
    <ol title="To log in to your Control Panel:">
      <li>Start your Web browser.</li>
      <li>Type <em type="bold">https://your_domain/ControlPanel/</em> in the address bar; then press <em type="bold">Enter</em>. (Replace

your_domain with your domain name). The Login window appears.
      </li>
      <li>Type your user ID and password in the appropriate fields.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Login</em>. The Control Panel appears. If your user ID/password combination does not work and an error message

appears, contact Support.
      </li>
    </ol>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='3' title="How can I change my password?"><answer>
    <ol title="To change your password: ">
 <li><p>In the My Profile menu group, click <em type="bold">Change My Password</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Change My Password window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>Type your new password in the New Password field.</li>
      <li>Type your new password again in the Confirm Password field.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. A message appears informing you that your changes have been saved.
      </li>
    </ol>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='4'  title="How can I add an end user?" user_access_level='DA'><answer>
    <ol title="To add an End User: ">
   <p>
    <em type="bold">Important:</em> In order to keep your passwords secure, you should always log in to your Control Panel via https, not http.
   </p>

 <li><p>In the User Management menu group, click <em type="bold">Add End User</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Add End User: Profile window appears.</p>
		</li>
    <li>Type the new user's full name in the Full Name field.</li>
    <li>Type the user's login ID in the Login ID field.
	  <p>
        <em type="bold">Note:</em> If a prefix has been congifured for the domain admin, then it is indicated above the Login ID field. Usernames are limited to 16 characters, including prefix. The Login ID must be a unique name. If it matches a name you have already submitted for another user, the control panel displays an error message when you try to submit the name. 
      </p>
    </li>
    <li>Type the user's password in the Password field.</li>
    <li>Type the user's password again in the Confirm Password field.</li>
    <li><p>Type the user's disk space quota (in MB).</p>
      <p><em type="bold">Note:</em> If you give 0 MB of disk space to a user, the user will not have a disk space quota. Usage will
only be limited by the quota of the Server Admin or Domain Admin.</p>
	</li>
    <li>Select the privileges (Mail, FTP Access, Shell Access) that you want for this user.</li>
    <li>If you selected Shell Access, select the shell you want from the Shell Access drop-down list.</li>
    <li>Select the user's associated domain from the Domain drop-down list.</li>
    <li>Click <em type="bold">Next</em>. If the user has mail privileges, the Add End User Mail Setup window appears with the mailbox name and email address in the appropriate fields.
    </li>
    <li>Select the Mail applications (Webmail, SpamAssassin, Clam AntiVirus) you want for this user.</li>
    <li>Click <em type="bold">Next</em>. The Add End User Preview window appears displaying the information you have selected for this user. If all the information is correct, go to the next step. To change the Mail Applications information, click <em type="bold">Previous</em> and make the desired changes, then click <em type="bold">Next</em> to go to the Preview window. To change any other information, click <em type="bold">Previous</em> twice to get to the Profile window and make any desired changes, then click <em type="bold">Next</em> twice to go to the Preview window.
    </li>
    <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. The User List window appears with a message informing you that the user has been added.
    </li>
    </ol>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='5'  title="How can I add a domain administrator?" user_access_level='SA'><answer>
    <ol title="To add a Domain Administrator: ">

   <p>
    <em type="bold">Important:</em> In order to keep your passwords secure, you should always log in to your Control Panel via https, not http.
   </p>
 <li><p>In the User Management menu group, click <em type="bold">Add Domain Admin</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Add Domain Admin: Profile window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>Type the new user's full name in the Full Name field.</li>
      <li>Type the user's login ID in the Login ID field.</li>
      <li>Type the user's password in the Password field.</li>
      <li>Type the user's password again in the Confirm Password field.</li>
      <li><p>Type the user's disk space quota (in MB).</p>
      <p><em type="bold">Note:</em> If you give 0 MB of disk space to a user, the user will not have a disk space quota. Usage will
only be limited by the quota of the Server Admin or Domain Admin.</p>
	  </li>
      <li>Select the privileges (Mail, FTP Access, Shell Access, etc) that you want for this user.
	  <p><em type="bold">Note: </em>If you selected Shell Access, select the default user shell from the Shell Access drop-down list.</p></li>
	  <li>Select the privileges (Mail, FTP Access, Shell Access, etc) you wish to allow this domain admin to offer to end users.</li>
	  <li>To add a prefix to the username of all users created by this domain admin, type the desired prefix in the End User Prefix field.
	  <p><em type="bold">Note: </em>Only use alphanumeric characters as well as _, -, and . in prefixes. Usernames are limited to 16 characters, including prefix. Only the System Administrator can create and change the prefix associated with domain administrators.</p></li>
	  <li>Type the first domain name this domain admin will administer in the Domain field.</li>
	  <li>Select the IP address for the domain from the IP Address drop-down menu.</li>
	  <li>Type any comments for this user in the Comments field.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Next</em>. The Mail Setup window appears containing the Mailbox Name for the domain administrator, an associated email address, and a Mail Applications section that enables you to turn on or off the Webmail client, filtering, and antivirus features.</li>
      <li>If you wish to change the default email address, type a different address in the Email Address field.</li>
      <li>If you wish to change the default mail applications, de-select the checkboxes for Webmail client, SpamAssassin, and/or Clam 

Antivirus.</li>
<li>Click <em type="bold">Next</em>. The Domain Setup window appears containing the Domain Alias option, the Web Services options, the End 

Users options, the Email Addresses options, the Website Logs options, the Domain Contact, and Mail Catchall options.
      </li>

<li>Select <em type="bold">Enable www domain alias</em> if you want to ensure that domain administrators typing the www. prefix or just 

typing the domain name will arrive at the domain you have created.</li>
<li>Select <em type="bold">CGI</em> or <em type="bold">SSL</em> if you want the domain administrator to be able to use either 

feature.</li>
<li>Type the number of email addresses the domain administrator can create by in the <em type="bold">Maximum number of email addresses</em> 

field, or allow the domain administrator an unlimited number by selecting the other option in this section.</li>
<li>Select <em type="bold">Do not create or store website logs</em> if you do not want logs created for the domain administrator's site.</li>
<li>Select <em type="bold">Create and store website logs</em> if you want logs created for the domain administrator's site.</li>
<li>Select <em type="bold">Never rotate website logs</em> if you do not want new logs created at intervals for the domain administrator's 

site.</li>
<li>Select <em type="bold">Rotate</em> and click the drop-down arrows to specify the interval you want to rotate and the number of days you 

want to save logs for the domain administrator's site.</li>

      <li>Select <em type="bold">Reject mail</em> if you want all misdirected mail returned to sender with an unknown user message.
      </li>
 <li>Select <em type="bold">Silently discard mail</em> if you want all misdirected mail deleted without a message returned to 

sender.
      </li>
 <li>Select <em type="bold">Deliver mail to Domain Admin</em> if you want all misdirected mail sent to the domain administrator's 

address.
      </li>
 <li>Select <em type="bold">Deliver mail to:</em> if you want all misdirected mail sent to an email address you type in the Deliver 

mail to: field.
      </li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Next</em>. The Add Domain Admin: Preview window appears with all of the options you have chosen.
      </li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Previous</em> if you want to go back and make changes.
      </li>
  <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em> if you want to save the information.
      </li>

  <li>Click <em type="bold">Save and Create Another</em> if you want to save the information and create another domain administrator.
      </li>
  <li>Click <em type="bold">Cancel</em> if you want to cancel your changes.
      </li>

    </ol>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='6'  title="How can I add a new domain?" user_access_level='SA'><answer>
    <ol title="To add a Virtual Host Domain: ">

 <li><p>In the Domain Management menu group, click <em type="bold">Add Domain</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The Add Domain Setup window appears.</p>
		</li>
    <li>Next to Domain Admin, from the Add the domain to the following user drop-down list, select the domain administrator.</li>
    <li>Next to Domain, type the user's domain name.<p>
        <em type="bold">Note:</em> After a domain is added, the domain name cannot be changed.
      </p>
    </li>
	<li>Next to IP Address, select the IP address for the domain.</li>
    <li>Next to Web Services, select the web services you want to enable. Enabling CGI permits CGI scripts in the domain's cgi-bin directory. Enabling SSL permits secure HTTPS connection using a shared certificate.</li>
    <li>Next to End Users, select the number of end users you want to allow the domain administrator to create.</li>
    <li>Next to Email Addresses, select the number of email addresses you want to allow the domain administrator to create.</li>
    <li>Next to Website Logs, select the Website log options you want.</li>
	<ul>
		<li>Select <em type="bold">Do not create or store website logs</em> if you do not want the site to use logs.</li>
		<li>Select <em type="bold">Create and store website logs</em> if you want to use third-party stats packages.</li>
		<li>Select <em type="bold">Never rotate website logs</em> if you do not want to delete any logs.</li>
		<li>Click <em type="bold">Rotate</em> and select the frequency of the log rotation you want from the associated drop-down menu. </li>
		<li>Select the number of logs you want to save from the <em type="bold">and save</em> drop-down menu.</li>
	</ul>
    <li>Next to Domain Contact, type the email address of the person to be contacted if error messages are generated for the domain.</li>
    <li>Next to Mail Catchall, select the option you want.
	<ul>
		<li>Select <em type="bold">Reject mail - return as unknown user</em> if you want misaddressed mail returned to the user with an “unknown user” reply message.</li>
		<li>Select <em type="bold">Silently discard mail</em> if you want misaddressed mail deleted without a reply message sent to the sender.</li>
		<li>Select <em type="bold">Deliver mail to Domain Admin</em> if you want misaddressed mail sent to the email address of the domain administrator.</li>
		<li>Select <em type="bold">Deliver mail to:</em> if you want misaddressed mail delivered to the email address you type in the associated field. If you type multiple addresses, separate each one with a comma.</li>
	</ul>
    <p><em type="bold">Note:</em> If you type multiple addresses, separate each one with a comma.
      </p>
    </li>
    <li>When you are finished, click <em type="bold">Next</em>. The Add Domain Preview window appears displaying the options you have selected for this domain. To make any changes, click <em>Previous</em>, make the desired changes, then click <em type="bold">Next</em> to go to the Preview window.
    </li>
    <li>Click <em type="bold"> Save/Create Another</em> if you want to create another domain. A message appears confirming that the domain has been added and the window refreshes with blank fields. If you do not want to create another domain, click <em type="bold">Save</em>. A message appears confirming that the domain has been added.
    </li>

    </ol>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='7'  title="How can I edit a user?" user_access_level='DA'><answer>
    <ol title="To edit an end user's properties: ">
 <li><p>In the User Management menu group, click <em type="bold">User List</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The User List window appears.</p>
		</li>
      <li>Select the Domain Admin and the domain you want from the drop-down list and click <em type="bold">Go</em>. The User List window for

the selected domain appears.
      </li>
      <li>Click properties for the user you want to edit. The Properties window appears.</li>
      <li>Next to Profile, click <em type="bold">Edit</em>. The Edit Profile window for the selected user appears.
      </li>
      <li>If you want to change the password, type the user's new password in the Password and Confirm Password fields.</li>
      <li><p>Type the user's new disk space quota (in MB) in the User Disk Space Field.</p>
      <p><em type="bold">Note:</em> If you give 0 MB of disk space to a user, the user will not have a disk space quota. Usage will
only be limited by the quota of the Server Admin or Domain Admin.</p>
	  </li>
      <li>Check the privileges (Mail, FTP Access, Shell Access) that you want for this user.</li>
      <li>If you selected Shell Access, select the shell you want from the Shell Access drop-down list.</li>
      <li>Select the user's associated domain from the Domain drop-down list.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. The Properties window appears with a message informing you that the domain has been changed.
      </li>
      <li>To edit the mail settings, next to Mail Setup, click <em type="bold">Edit</em>. The Edit Mail Setup window for the selected domain

appears.
      </li>
      <li>Select the mail applications (Webmail, SpamAssassin, Clam AntiVirus) you want for this user.</li>
      <li>Click <em type="bold">Save</em>. The Properties window appears with a message informing you that the domain has been changed.
      </li>
    </ol>
  </answer></question>
  <question  id='8' title="How can I edit a domain?" user_access_level='SA'><answer>
    <ol title="To edit a Domain Admin's properties: ">

    <p>
    <em type="bold">Important:</em> In order to keep your passwords secure, you should always log in to your Control Panel via https, not http.
   </p>

 <li><p>In the User Management menu group, click <em type="bold">User List</em> (expand the menu group to see the links, if necessary). For more information about expanding and collapsing menu groups, see <a topic='menus_navigation'>Menus and Navigation</a>.</p>
		<p>The User List window appears.</p>
		</li>
    <li>Click <em type="bold">properties</em> for the Domain Admin you want to edit. The Properties window for the selected Domain Admin appears.
    </li>
    <li>Next to Profile, click <em type="bold">Edit</em>. The Edit Profile window for the selected domain administrator appears.
    </li>
    <li>If you want to change the user name, next to Full Name, type the name you want.</li>
    <li>You cannot change the Login ID.</li>
    <li>If you want to change the password, type the new password in the Password and Confirm Password fields.</li>
    <li><p>If you want to change the disk space quota, type the new quota (in MB) in the User Disk Space field.</p>
      <p><em type="bold">Note:</em> If you give 0 MB of disk space to a user, the user will not have a disk space quota. Usage will
only be limited by the quota of the Server Admin or Domain Admin.</p>
	</li>
    <li>Check the privileges (Mail, FTP Access, Shell Access, etc.) that you want for this domain administrator.</li>
    <li>If you selected Shell Access, select the shell you want from the Shell Access drop-down list.</li>
    <li>Check the privileges (Mail, FTP Access, Shell Access, etc.) that you want this domain administrator to be able to make available to end users.</li>
	<li>To add or edit a prefix for the username of all users created by this domain admin, type or edit the desired prefix in the End User Prefix field.
	  <p><em type="bold">Note: </em>Only use alphanumeric characters as well as _, -, and . in prefixes. Usernames are limited to 16 characters, including prefix. Only the System Administrator can create and change the prefix associated with domain administrators.</p></li>
    <li>Type any comments for this user in the Comments field.</li>
    <li>When you are finished editing, click <em type="bold">Save</em>. The Properties window appears with a message informing you that the domain has been changed.
    </li>
    <li>To edit the mail settings, next to Mail Setup, click <em type="bold">Edit</em>. The Edit Mail Setup window for the selected user appears.
    </li>
    <li>Select the mail applications (Webmail, SpamAssassin, Clam AntiVirus) you want for this domain administrator.</li>
    <li>When you are finished editing, click <em type="bold">Save</em>. The Properties window appears with a message informing you that the user has been changed.
    </li>

    </ol>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='9'  title="How many users can I add to my server?" user_access_level='SA'><answer>
    <p>Technically, while there is no hard limit to the number of users you can add to your account, there are some practical limits. Each user

account requires processes. As the number of users grows and they become more active, server resources can become exhausted.</p>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='10' title="How many domains can I add to my server?" user_access_level='SA'><answer>
    <p>The maximum number of domains depends on the amount of traffic each domain receives. There is no set maximum number of domains, but as

traffic increases for your domains, server resource consumption does as well. Your server may only be able to adequately serve one or two very

busy domains, or several hundred domains that have very light traffic.</p>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='11' title="What is the difference between a system administrator user, domain administrator user, and an end user?"

user_access_level='SA'><answer>
    <ul title="The differences between types of users are:">
      <li>The system administrator user controls all other users, domains, files, groups, permissions, and settings for the entire server. This

user has all the features of the domain administrator and end users.</li>
      <li>A domain administrator user is created by the system administrator user and has control over one or more domains on the server and

the users associated with those domains. This user has all the features of end users.</li>
      <li>An end user is created by either a system administrator or domain administrator user and has email, FTP, or shell privileges.  They

are associated with a domain.</li>
    </ul>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='12' title="Is there virus scanning in the control panel?"><answer>
    <p>Yes. Enabling the Clam Antivirus service for a user will filter viruses to that user&#x2019;s Quarantine mail folder.</p>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='13' title="Will the control panel filter spam?"><answer>
    <p>Yes. Enabling the Spam Assassin service for a user will filter possible spam to that user&#x2019;s Junk mail folder.</p>
  </answer></question>
  <question id='14' title="Can I monitor my disk usage?"><answer>
    <p>Yes. After logging into the control panel, the disk usage is displayed in the top left corner of the interface.</p>
  </answer></question>
</category>
</faq>
